

Miroslav Krsmanovic

web designer / developer

devfolio ₫





Graphic designer with 5+ years of experience in brand id and web design. Skilled at Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop and Illustrator), Sketch, Figma... Starting my career at 99desgin, Freelancer.com, and then moving to Upwork I had the opportunity to work with more than 600 clients from all parts of the world.

Since last year my main preoccupation has been FrontEnd development because I always wanted to make my ideas live!:) I'm in process of learning React - loved the idea of component-based architecture!

Experience

Freelancer.com

2015-2019

Creating brands for various businesses.

UpWork.com

2015-2019

Web design and web development. Using WordPress as a primary technology for building simple web sites.

Greco

2019-present

UI/UX designer responsible for creating an intuitive, user-friendly web app. Developing wireframes and user journeys based on research and testing.

Education

Faculty of Security Studies

2009-2014

Univeristy of Belgrade. Bachelor degree

IT Academy

2017

Web desgin department. Getting familiar with basics principles

Computer School Vinca

2018

PHP and MySQL web application development

Computer School Vinca

2018

Course of WordPress. Theoretical and practical examination